I just want to apologize
for being so rude
(Emily:)the other day
in my office.
No, no. No need to apologize.
(Raj:)Excuse me,
can I say something?
(Raj:)I just love both you guys,
(Raj:)and I want you
to get along.
And when I say "love,"
I meant as a friend.
(Raj:)And, uh, way
too soon, right?
(Penny:)Okay, sit down.
Listen, Emily,
(Penny:)what happened
between me and Raj
(Penny:)was a long time ago.
It was,
(Raj:)and I may have
made it seem
(Raj:)like a bigger deal
than I should have.
(Penny:)Yeah, and Leonard and I
are engaged now,
(Penny:)and I'm just hoping we can put
this whole thing behind us.
(Emily:)Mm. I'd like that, too.
(Emily:)Yeah, I thought
I'd be okay with it,
(Emily:)but then I saw
how pretty you are.
(Penny:)Oh, that's so sweet.
(Penny:)I mean, look at you--
you are gorgeous.
(Raj:)It's true--
you're both gorgeous.
(Raj:)Kind of says something about
the man who could bed you both.
(chuckles)
(Raj:)You get why I've been alone
most of my adult life.